Family requires sacrifices.
Bring Her Back is a horror film directed by Danny Philippou.
Following the death of their father, a brother and sister are sent to live with a
foster mother, only to learn that she is hiding a terrifying secret.
Andy, played by Billy Barratt.
Laura, played by Sally Hawkins.
Cathy, played by Mischa Heywood.
Oliver, played by Jonah Wren Phillips.
Phil, played by Stephen Phillips.
Wendy, played by Sally-Anne Upton.
Bring Her Back is a 2025 Australian supernatural folk horror film directed by Danny and
Michael Philippou, the former of whom co-wrote the screenplay with Bill Hinzman.
It stars Billy Barratt, Sora Wong, Jonah Wren Phillips, and Sally Hawkins.
The film follows two step-siblings who find themselves orphaned and placed in
the middle of an occult ritual by their new foster mother.
Bring Her Back was theatrically released by Sony Pictures
Releasing International in Australia on 29 May 2025.
The film received positive reviews, with Hawkins's performance being highlighted
for praise, and grossed $39.1 million on a budget of $15 million.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship,
ritual, supernatural, death of father, grief.
The tone is dark.